[
    {
      "question": "Is SAP Build Process Automation a low-code and no-code application development tool?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correctAnswer": ["Yes"],
      "type": "single",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Lobby page in SAP Build used for?",
      "options": ["to create, access and, manage projects", "to book meeting rooms", "to configure database servers"],
      "correctAnswer": ["to create, access and, manage projects"],
      "type": "single",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The sales order approval process is automated using SAP BPA without using forms?",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": ["True"],
      "type": "single",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"What roles are available for SAP Build Process Automation?",
      "options":["ProcessAutomationAdmin", "ProcessAutomationDeveloper","ProcessAutomationUser","ProcessAutomationTester","ProcessAutomationParticipant"],
      "correctAnswer":["ProcessAutomationAdmin","ProcessAutomationDeveloper", "ProcessAutomationParticipant" ],
      "type":"multiple",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"What is a business process?",
      "options":["An intelligent bot to automate repetitive manual processes", "A configurable template", "A repetitive set of tasks or activities that are completed to achieve a goal or outcome for a business"],
      "correctAnswer":["A repetitive set of tasks or activities that are completed to achieve a goal or outcome for a business"],
      "type":"single",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"What are some of the available Layout and/or Input fields available in forms?",
      "options":["Headlines", "Number" ,"Date", "Video", "Dropdown"],
      "correctAnswer":["Headlines", "Number" ,"Date"],
      "type":"multiple",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"In SAP Build Process Automation, forms can be utilized:",
      "options":["to start the process", "to approve or reject a task","to notify requestor","to send emails"],
      "correctAnswer":["to start the process", "to approve or reject a task","to notify requestor"],
      "type":"multiple",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"Which configurations are necessary for process condition?",
      "options":["Add a condition to the process", "Configure if and else conditions","Define the process flow for different conditional paths","Map the condition input with process content","Add environment variables"],
      "correctAnswer":["Add a condition to the process", "Configure if and else conditions","Define the process flow for different conditional paths"],
      "type":"multiple",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"Is the form link to run the business process generated before deploying the package?",
      "options":["Yes","No"],
      "correctAnswer":["No"],
      "type":"single",
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"Where can an end user work on the forms?",
      "options":["Chat Bot","Monitor Workflow Application","My Inbox","Process Workspace"],
      "correctAnswer":["My Inbox"],
      "type":"single",
      "points": 1
    }
]